

# Vrushabh Virkar

**B.Tech Student** 

Organized and Dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude.Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.Experienced and results-driven professional with a strong background in front-end development and proficiency in Programming language.

virkarvrushabh2002@gmail.com

Ambazari Hilltop, Nagpur, India

facebook.com/Vrushabh Virkar

9665273616

**SKILLS** 

Python

in linkedin.com/in/vrushabh-virkar-b0a3b8226

(O) instagram.com/virkarvrushabh

C/C++ Programming Language

SQL/MYSQL

Operating Systems (Windows, Linux, Unix)

# **EDUCATION**

# **B.Tech**

Guru Nanak Institute of Engineering and Technology

12/2021 - Present Nagpur

Computer Science And Engineering

B.Tech

**Higher Secondary** 

Tuljaram Chaturchand College Of Arts, Science & Commerce

06/2019 - 08/2021

Science

• 11th and 12th Science

# PERSONAL PROJECTS

#### Calculator

 This calculator can perform basic mathematical operations like addition, subtraction, multiplication, and division.

Java Programming

OOPs

we use HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to build calculator webpage.

# Number guessing game in Python

• It select random number from range and we need to Guess.

#### Password Generator Using Java

**CERTIFICATES** 

developement technologies.

(07/2023 - 10/2023)

Useful for generating Strong Password.

Java Full Stack Developer course

C/C++ Programming Language Course

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Java Developer Intern Slash Mark

11/2023 - 02/2024 India ,Virtual

Slash mark is leading company which provides virtual internship in collaboration with AICTE. It assign intern projects on specific domain in three levels easy, intermediate and Advanced.

Tasks

o completing assigned java project like 1.Password Generator, 2.Employment Management tool.

Contact: slashmark.cloud

# Internpe, virtual

07/2023 - 08/2023 India.Virtual

Working on front-end web development projects like calculator, ecommerce website,etc

developing and designing web pages.

Web development intern

Contact: www.internpe.in

# This course introduce to c/c++ syntax and OOPs. Developer and Technology Virtual Experience

Debugging Code, Software development and methodology: Waterfall and Agile, Algorithmic thinking, Software development lifecycle.

This course introduce to front-end, middleware, and back-end Java web

#### Solution Architecture Virtual Experience Program (04/2023 - 04/2023)

Hosting architecture, Solution Architecture.

Programme (07/2023 - 07/2023)

# Python with Data Analytics Intern Revat Networks

05/2023 - 06/2023

India,Nagpur

Baramati, Pune (MS)

It is Training platform, which helps students to learn and perform.

• Get to know about python and it's different libraries.

Contact: Mr.Raj Arora. - revatnetwork.com

# LANGUAGES

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Playing volleyball

Coding